2023, while the invocation by Reverend of All-Sight's Biscuit Church, Ms. Mays'
and William.
Let us pray.
Gracious God, we thank you for the city of Mayama.
Thank you for our mayor, city council members, city employees, the businesses, the churches,
the families, and the individuals that make our city the community that it is.
We pray for this council meeting tonight.
We ask you to give the council members wisdom and guidance as they deliberate on the items
before them.
May every decision be righteous in your sight for our benefit and for your glory.
We ask this in the name of the Father and of the Son and of the Holy Spirit.
Amen.
I pledge allegiance to the flag of the United States of America and to the Republic for which
it stands, one nation under God, in the visit of Israel, with liberty and justice
and so on.
We're four above the computer, let's get to a personal imperative.
5, Klein Blitz, most to approve.
5.
Williams?
Okay.
9.
10.
7.
from September 3rd, 2023 through September 26th, 2023 on behalf of the City of Miami.
Focusing on review, pleadings, filings, and other documentation, preparing responses and communicating
with the Miami team related to the following, which were the dam safety issues, the
release to the study plan, the contaminated sediment transport study, Indian Hoffmanment in the
Circuit Court of Appeals, followed up. So as you can tell, it was a very active, improductive
September. However, this $19,572 would go against our current budget. If this claim were approved,
it would have a remaining balance of $637,491.95 for fiscal year, 2023, 2024.
and so it is well within our budget at a moment.
Thank you, motion we approve.
Second.
Perfect.
Bye.
Williams.
Hi.
Dougal.
East.
Hi.
Eight.
Renew.
Annual contracts.
21.
That fits for.
With Linda Mayfield Davis.
For as needs, veterinary services.
For fiscal year 2324.
The three year contract with, while I say three years, up to three years,
that we can renew the contract this will be the third year.
So next spring, we would go out for bids for his services.
Something just how long history is to how far that we've been into this.
This will be the third year.
This is all for the.
Um.
Yes.
Yeah.
Thank you.
Bye.
Williams.
Dougal.
East.
Hi.
Nine award contract agreement to clean uniform for RFQ23-53.
The uniform services.
Continued upon the submission of all required contract documents in the
Proof of the city manager.
Or he does need to sign the contract and notice two proceed.
We had sent these out to send us airmark and clean.
Clean was the only company that had given us a bid.
And they were actually our current company that would go business with.
Um.
These here.
And you can see that there's a charge that they do for insurance on.
If the shirts get destroyed or lost and so on that they cut that price and have.
They went on on two items.
They went down on just just about all the rest of everything else.
So it they only will do contracts for a year.
I couldn't get them to do a six month contract.
And the most appropriate.
I got to do the same thing.
It was just one page, right?
Just one.
So I just got two of them.
You reckon it is a volume issue?
The other companies wouldn't bid.
I just likely banks have been slow to install them.
You know, I'll ask them later.
I'll see your mid-towns.
I just say I'm sorry.
I had one guy last time called after the mids were submitted.
He said, hey can I still bid?
I can't.
I have to think that everybody are pretty tight right now on employees.
So that's that there was a little bit of cost savings associated with this.
Yeah.
I make a motion made proof.
That's what you write, man.
Pardon?
You write, man.
That's what you write.
Yeah.
You know, we can always go out and rebuild.
But in this situation, I think that they've been a good provider on everything so far.
And yeah, I would recommend going on.
I'll second.
All right.
Williams?
Dunk old?
All right.
East.
10, 20, 20, 24, medium schedule.
So that's in our packet.
And I know at one time we used to have these on Tuesdays.
And I think I was the reason we changed it for Mondays.
And then we kept it for Mondays for Brian's situation.
Yeah, I know his situation changed too, just today.
So do we want to try to go back to Tuesdays?
You can't.
All right.
I think we had two scenarios with Brian and Kevin both that.
And I had a conversation with this with staff when we reviewed this.
And we were basically going to leave it up at the council.
But staff had no reason compelling to move it.
Everything's been working fine.
You know, in the past we had an extra day.
I think with Monday to get things prepared ready instead of just having that over the weekend.
But I think we've gotten pretty used to that.
And then, see if it seems to work out just fine.
Okay.
We'll do it either way.
I'll make a motion to approve.
Second.
Perfect.
Hi.
Williams.
He's dead.
Hi.
11.
On the new business of any, which is residence, supposed to be a
agenda.
12 staff reports.
13 trusted community announcements.
14 of German.
Second.
Hi.
Williams.
All right.